# **MATTHEW DAVENPORT**

**Phone:** 0401181104

**Email:** matthew.davenport30@gmail.com

Address: 19 Gresham Street East Brisbane, Brisbane, 4169

#### **PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY**

A trustworthy, dependable, responsible staffer with 4 years of experience providing ongoing support and work. Dedicated, tireless professional with a keen ability to maximize both time and business efficiencies. Well-organized with in-depth technical knowledge and keen attention to detail. I have experience managing an office conducting administrative work and dealing with members of the public on an ongoing and continuous basis. My time management and work ethic are second-to-none, being able to assist the office when called upon.

## **EDUCATION**

**Present** Bachelor of Information Technology: User Experience Design

• University of Queensland - Brisbane, Queensland

**Dec. 2016** Government & International Relations

• Griffith University - Brisbane, QLD

Dec. 2015

• Anglican Church Grammar School (Churchie) - Brisbane, Queensland

## **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

Jun. 2018 – Present BRISBANE CITY, Queensland

#### Admin and Membership Assistant, Liberal National Party Headquarters

- Maintain and update the LNP Membership databases, as well as dealing with any incoming issues or concerns.
- Administration support to the State Party Secretary.
- Greet visitors or callers and handle their inquiries or direct them to the appropriate persons according to their needs, as well as maintaining scheduling and event calendars.

Feb. 2019 – May. 2019 Brisbane, Queensland

#### Campaign Assistant, Liberal National Party Headquaters

Assisting in the 2019 federal election campaign. Assisted in roles from websites, research tasks, campaigning, and reports.

#### May. 2018 – Jun. 2018 Kenmore, Brisbane, Queensland

#### Assistant Electorate Officer (Job Fill), Kenmore Electorate Office

- Job fill role while staff was on holidays, working under State Member for Moggill, Dr Christian Rowan MP
- Perform general office duties, such as taking or transcribing dictation, typing or proofreading correspondence, distributing or filing official forms, or scheduling appointments.

#### Dec. 2017 – Feb. 2018 Gold Coast, Queensland

#### Assistant Electorate Officer, Bonney Electorate Office

- Respond to requests for information from the public, other municipalities, state officials, or state and federal legislative offices.
- Perform general office duties, such as taking or transcribing dictation, typing or proofreading correspondence, distributing or filing official forms, or scheduling appointments.

## Jul. 2016 – Dec. 2017 Brisbane, Queensland

#### **Event Day Staff, Stadiums Queensland**

Working as a casual event day staff provides me with the opportunity to interact
with new people, and specifically showcase quality customer service that the
Gabba promotes. Whether it be an usher or a gate person, customer service is
the number one priority for the staff.

## Aug. 2016 - Nov. 2017 Redlands, Queensland

#### Intern, Redlands Electorate Office

- Intern under the instruction of the MP Matthew McEachan of the Redlands electorate. My internship consisted of working with the team members on the day to day activities.
- General office work, emails, phone calls, letters and meeting with constituents.
   Perform general office duties, such as taking or transcribing dictation, typing or proofreading correspondence, distributing or filing official forms, or scheduling appointments.

## Jul. 2014 – Feb. 2017 Brisbane, Queensland

#### Crew Member, McDonalds Australia

Food service worker with exceptional interpersonal skills. Reliable, punctual and works well under pressure. As well as excellent communication skills and rapid and precise customer service skills.

## **SKILLS**

Time Management	Expert	Communication	Expert
Prioritizing and Multitasking	Expert	General Office Work	Expert
Adobe Suite	Experienced	Javascript	Experienced
Microsoft Office Suite	Expert	Administration	Expert
SQL/ MySQL	Skillful	HTML/ CSS	Experienced

## **ACCOMPLISHMENTS + AFFILIATIONS**

Responsible Serving of Alcohol SITHFAB201 (RSA) - Recieved 2016

Responsible Gaming Services SITHGAM201 (RSG) - Received 2016

First Aid Certificate - Received 2016 (to be updated)

Numerous Army Cadet Awards (2012-2015)

Queensland Certificate of Education - Received 2015

Churchie Old Boys Association (OBA)

## **REFERENCES**

Matt McEachan Former Member for Redlands Mobile – 0432 585 140

Gary Gaudion OH&S Officer Email - gg@gaudion.com.au Mobile - 0411 140 150

Sam O'Connor MP Member for Bonney Email - bonney@parliament.qld.gov.au Mobile - 0416 925 981